Nepal Church History Project Archives
Yale University Divinity School Library
- G - Photograph Collection, Series VII
  - G 02 The Church Inside Nepal
    - G 02 03 10 Para-Church Organizations - NBCBS (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - G 02 03 11 Para-Church Organizations - Operation Mobilization (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - G 02 03 12 Para-Church Organizations - Bethany Orphanage (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - G 02 03 13 Para-Church Organizations - Christian Media, Nepal (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - G 02 03 14 Para-Church Organizations - International Needs (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - G 02 03 15 Para-Church Organizations - Samdan Publishing / Bardan Music Ministries (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - G 02 04 01 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - Bible Schools, Baglung and DVBS, 1965, 1967, 1971, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 04 02 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - Good News Festival, Kathmandu, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 04 03 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - Sunday School Teachers' Training (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 04 04 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - First Christian March, Kathmandu, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 04 05 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - ACTS Congress (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 04 06 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - Nepal 2000 COE (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 04 07 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - Eastern Nepal Evangelism Campaign (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 04 08 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - Survey of Churches (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - G 02 05 01 Dandeldhura (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - G 02 06 01 Dhangadi (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - G 02 07 01 Tikapur & Gyani Shah (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - G 02 08 01 Ghorahi (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - G 02 09 01 Nawal Parasi (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - G 02 10 01 Butwal (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - G 02 11 01 Tansen (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - G 02 12 01 Paimey (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - G 02 13 01 Pokhara (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - G 02 14 01 Gorkha (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - G 02 15 01 Putali Sadak (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - G 02 16 01 Gyaneshwar (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - G 02 17 01 Patan (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - G 02 18 01 Aradhana (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - G 02 19 01 Bhaktapur (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - G 02 20 01 Anandaban (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - G 02 21 01 Okhaldhunga (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - G 02 22 01 Dharan (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - G 02 23 01 Jhapa (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - G 02 24 01 Dhankuta (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - G 02 25 01 Village churches (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - G 03 The Nepali Church Outside Nepal from 1990
    - G 03 01 01 Himalaya 2000 & HIM-COE - General (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - G 03 01 02 Himalaya 2000 & HIM-COE - Women's Ministry (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - G 03 01 03 Himalaya 2000 & HIM-COE - Youth Ministry (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - G 03 02 01 Western Himalayas (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - G 03 03 01 Urban India - Delhi (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - G 03 03 02 Urban India - Calcutta (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - G 03 03 03 Urban India - Bangalore (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - G 03 03 04 Urban India - Nagpur (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - G 03 03 05 Urban India - Varanasi (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - G 03 03 06 Urban India - Lucknow (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - G 03 03 07 Urban India - Mumbai (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - G 03 03 08 Urban India - Gonda (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - G 03 04 01 Darjeeling District (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - G 03 05 01 Sikkim (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - G 03 06 01 Duars (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - G 03 07 01 North-East India - Megalaya (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - G 03 07 02 North-East India - Assam (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - G 03 07 03 North-East India - Manipur (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - G 03 07 04 North-East India - Mizoram (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - G 03 08 01 Myanmar / Burma (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - G 03 09 01 Malaysia (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - G 03 10 01 Hong Kong (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Additional Photographs
    - Album: "Record of Miss Isobel Ritchie's visit from Ganglok to the Finnish Mission work in Sikkim, October/November 1933" (Box 45, Folder 11)
- H - Book and Pamphlet Collection, Series VIII
  See listing at repository
- I - Nepali Bible and Hymnal/Songbook Collection, Series IX
  - I 01 Bibles and Scripture Portions in Nepali and Other Languages of Nepal
    - I 01 01 01 New Testament (Box 46)
    - I 01 01 01 New Testament (Box 47)
    - I 01 01 02 Matthew (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - I 01 01 03 Mark (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - I 01 01 04 Luke (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - I 01 01 05 John (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - I 01 01 06 Acts (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - I 01 01 07 Romans, Corinthians & other New Testament (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - I 01 02 01 Old Testament (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - I 01 02 02 Psalms (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - I 01 02 03 Genesis & other Old Testament Books (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - I 01 03 01 Whole Bible (Box 50)
    - I 01 04 01 Catholic translations (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - I 01 05 01 Gurung (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - I 01 05 02 Lepcha (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - I 01 05 03 Lhasa Tibetan (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - I 01 05 04 Limbu (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - I 01 05 05 Magar (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - I 01 05 06 Newari (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - I 01 05 07 Sunwar (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - 1 01 05 08 Tamang (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 1 01 05 09 Maithili (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 1 01 05 10 Hindi (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - I 02 Song / Hymn Books in Nepali and Other Languages of Nepal
    - I 02 01 01 Song / Hymn Books published in Darjeeling and other parts of India (Box 53)
    - I 02 01 01 Song / Hymn Books published in Darjeeling and other parts of India (Box 54)
    - I 02 02 01 Song / Hymn Books published in Nepal (Box 54)
- Regarding the NCHP Project, Series X
  - General Material, 1986, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Contains information related to the Security Policy and to a CD of digitized project documents.
  - Correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Cindy Perry Research Outlines and Notes, c.1980-1999 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Cindy Perry Lists of Materials in the Collection (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Sample Listing of A materials, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Addendum, Series XI
  - A - Church in Nepal
    - A 01 14 01 Duncan Hospital Raxaul, 1930s, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Raxaul Medical Mission
    - A 01 24 Chas Tanner, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - A 02 02 01 Interserve, 2005-2007 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - A 02 06 01 INF - Church-related, 1990-1991 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - A 02 07 01 The Leprosy Mission, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - A 02 16 01 Wycliffe, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - A 02 19 01 Nepal Leprosy Fellowship, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - A 02 21 01 Maya Leprosy Fund, 2004-2006 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - A 03 08 01 FOCUS, 2004-2006 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - A 03 13 01 HDCS (NCF), n.d. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - A 03 17 01 NBCBS, 1990-2004 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - A 03 18 01 NCCEF / Bal Sangati, 1984-1989 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - A 03 20 01 Nepal Campus Crusade For Christ, 1966-1979 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - A 03 22 01 Nepal Evangelistic Teams, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - A 03 23 01 Nepal Every Home Concern, 1994-2007 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - A 03 31 07 Orphanages - New Life Home, 1997-2006 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - A 03 35 01 Teach Ministries, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - A 03 68 01 Missions Commission of Nepal, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - A 03 69 01 Nepal Mission Training Center, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - A 03 71 01 Early Childhood Education Centre, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - A 03 72 01 His Worshippers, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - A 03 73 01 Children at Risk in Nepal, ca.2000 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - A 03 74 01 Nepal Fellowship for the Handicapped, 2002-2006 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - A 04 01 01 Church Files - General Historical, 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - A 04 01 05 Church Files - 1980-1989, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - A 04 01 07 Church Files - 2000-2009, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - A 04 03 01 Assembly of God & Discipleship Training Centre, Kathmandu, 1973 - 1985 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - A 04 05 01 Evangelical Christian Alliance of Nepal / Four-Square, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - A 04 08 04 National Churches Fellowship Nepal, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - A 04 10 01 Nepal Christian Society, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - A 04 18 01 NCCN, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - A 05 07 01 Bhaktapur, Pastor Tir Bahadur Deew..., 2005 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - A 05 16 01 Ghorahi, Dang, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - A 05 17 01 Gyaneshwar, Kathmandu / Nepali Isai Mandali, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - A 05 21 01 Kathmandu Valley - Miscellanceous Churches, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - A 05 47 01 Anandit church, Koteshwar, Kathmandu, 2003-2006 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - A 05 48 01 Kathmandu International Church, 2003-2006 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - A 06 01 01 Individual Nepali Christians General (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - A 06 24 01 Paudel, Resham Raj & Sita, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - A 06 29 01 Pradhan, Prem - General, 1965-1966 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - A 06 38 01 Rokaya, Kali Bahadur & Draupadi, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - A 06 66 01 Sharma, Bal Krishna, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - A 06 74 01 Bhuvan, Sunira & Abhishika Devkota, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - A 07 01 01 ABEN & Consultation on Theological Education in Nepal, 1993, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - A 07 06 01 DBCI / NBCI, ca.1983 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - A 07 15 01 NBI / NBA, 1994-1995 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - A 07 17 01 Nepal Theological Seminary, P.O. Box 3535, Kathmandu / Nepal Ebenezer Bible College, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - A 08 15 01 Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - A 09 06 01 Himalayan Mission, Inc., 1999 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - A 09 10 01 Prayer Fellowship For South Asia, 2005-2007 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - A 10 14 01 Vijay Press & Jill James & Pat Cook Prayer Letters, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - A 11 01 01 Nepali Law & Religious Freedom, 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - A 11 05 01 Miscellaneous, 1998-2001 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - B - Diaspora
    - B 01 01 01 Himalaya 2000 Movement & HIM-COE, 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - B 01 02 02 Prayer For Nepal (Global Network), 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - B 01 03 02 Himalayan Ministries - Prayer Letter, etc. (mainly Cindy Perry), 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - B 01 04 01 Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - B 01 06 05 Ron's Music & Youth On Fire & Four Corner Gurkha Mission, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - B 01 06 06 Shalom Ministries / Satish Chettri, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - B 02 01 07 Miscellanceous - Kalimpong & Darjeeling, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - B 02 01 13 Presbyterian Free Church & Himalayan Evangelical Fellowship, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - B 02 01 18 Kala Kriti - A Project of Waasta, 2003-2004 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - B 02 02 01 Sikkim General, 1992-2004 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - B 02 02 05 FECAI & Sikkim AD2000, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - B 02 03 03 Bhutan Churches, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - B 02 03 06 Bhutan Miscellaneous, 1989-2005 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - B 02 04 01 North-East India, 1999-2006 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - B 02 04 04 Urban India, 1998-2006 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - B 02 04 05 Assam, 2000-2004 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - B 02 04 07 Manipur, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - B 02 04 10 Shillong / Meghalaya, 2001-2004 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - B 02 05 01 Him Serve, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - B 03 01 02 Myanmar General, 1993-2004 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - B 03 02 05 Gurkhas - Cindy's Research Notes (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - B 03 03 01 Tibet Christian Ministry, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - B 03 04 01 Other Countries - General, 1996-1997 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - B 03 04 02 Korea, 1993-2000 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - B 03 04 03 Malaysia & Singapore, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - B 03 04 04 North America, 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - B 03 04 05 Persian Gulf, 1996-2004 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - B 03 04 08 Taiwan, 1995-2000 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - B 03 04 09 Thailand, 2000-2004 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - D - Nepali Christian Literature Collection
    - D 02 10 01 Nepal Every Home Concern (NEHC), n.d. (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - G - Photograph Collection
    - G 01 10 03; G 01 10 04; G 01 10 01; G 01 15 01 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      C of S Kalimpong; Kalimpong Orphanages; Sikkim/Bhutan Nor. MIssion; Gurkhas
    - G 01 05 03; G 01 06 01 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      Nautenwa; Raxaul
    - G 01 07 01; G 01 08 01; G 01 08 02; G 01 08 03 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      Assam/Shillong; EH Church - Mission (Church of Scotland; WEC Darjeeling
    - G 01 08 02 Darjeeling District - Eastern Himalayan Mission - 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - G 01 08 02 Darjeeling District - Eastern Himalayan Mission - 2 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - G 01 Miscellaneous Nepali Church Outside Nepal Prior to 1990 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - G 02 01 01 NCF Conference (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - G 02 02 01 Imprisonment (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - G 02 03 04 Para-Church Organizations - Nepal Prayer Fellowship (Box 59, Folder 3)
      Nepal Prayer Fellowship Women's Ministry and Early Nepal Bible Training
    - G 02 04 08 Special Events, Trainings & Conferences - Survey of Churches (Box 59, Folder 4)
      SCN Training and Dhangadi
    - G 02 11 01; G 02 12 01 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      Tansen; Pyersingh/Paimey
    - G 02 13 01 Pokhara - 1 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - G 02 13 01 Pokhara - 2 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - G 02 14 01; G 02 15 01; G 02 16 01 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      Gorkha; Putali Sadak, Gyaneshwar
    - G 02 18 01; G 02 19 04 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      Aradhana; Bhaktapur. Note on the folder says: Early Aradhana Mandali with Pastor Nicanor Tamang Bhaktapur
    - G 02 21 01; G 02 22 01 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      Okhaldunga; Dharan
    - G 02 General and G 02 03 01 Nepal Every Home Concern (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - G 02 Shops, Selling, Bridges, Buildings (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - G 02 Agriculture (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - G 02 Carrying People, Spinning and Weaving, Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - G 02 Kathmandu (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - G 02 Coolies (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - G 02 Miscellaneous, Aeroplanes, People, Tribes of Nepal (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - G 02 Hinduism, Buddhism (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - G 02 Water (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - G 02 Miscellaneous Scenery (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - G 02 Miscellaneous Trades and Events (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - G 02 Album - pictures and drawings (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - G 02 Miscellaneous pictures/articles (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - G 02 Village houses, Pioneers, Every day living (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - G 02 Bible Translators, NBF, ZBMay, WEC (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - G 02 NEB Darjeeling, WMPL & DHBS, Eliz. Franklin and team (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - G 03 01 01 HIM-COE General, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - G 03 08 01 Myanmar / Burma - 1, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      Cindy's first trip to Myanmar, 1993
    - G 03 08 01 Myandmar / Burma - 2, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - G 03 Diaspora and Cindy Perry, 1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - G 03 India / Himalayas (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - G 03 Bhutan (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - G 03 Church in India (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - G 03 07 North-East India - cultural scenes (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - G 03 04 01; G 03 05 01 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      Darjeeling/Kalimpong; Sikkim
    - G 03 05 01 Sikkim (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - G 03 Holy Palace near Nakalbari (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - G 03 01 Namchi (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - G 03 03 01 Nepali Church Urban (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - G 03 05 Sikkim; G 03 01 HIM-COE (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - G 03 01 02/03 HIM Prayer FEllowship, Delhi and Calcutta (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - G 03 06 01; G 03 07 01 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      Jalpaiguri/Jaigaon; Meghalaya
    - G 03 Diaspora Miscellaneous (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - G Unclassified photographs - 1 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - G Unclassified photographs - 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - G Photocopies of photographs (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - G Photographic negatives - 1 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - G Photographic negatives - 2 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - G Slides (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Album sheets and large mounted photographs (Box OV1)
    - Large photographs and posters - Nepal and Tibet (Box OVd-2)
  - H - Book and Pamphlet Collection
    - H 01 01 01 (Assorted articles), ca.1940s (Box 65, Folder 1)
      This material is also marked as part of the Himalayan Collection, Series A.
      Series of articles written by Paul J. Lindell and Katherien Harbord
    - H 01 02 01 (19 titles), 1906-1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      Many of these articles have numbers in the Himalayan Collection, Series A.
      Titles: Introductory Historical Statement in Visions & Victories in Hindustan by Brenton T. Badley (1931); Chapter II: Naini Tal by N. B. Waugh and M. E. Badley; Chapter XXIV: Pithoragarh by Lucy W. Sullivan; Chapter LVIII: Almora by E. S. Oakley; Things Touching the King: The Story of the Duchess of Teck Hospital by G. W. Emery and M. W. Anderson; A Wonderful Deliverance by J. H. Coombe; Calendar; Caste or Christ? Sketches of Indian life by John Z. Hodge and George E. Hicks (1906); The Cloud Moves by Kenneth Holmes (1974); The Cloud Moves by Kenneth Homes (earlier printing); Via Raxaul; Miscellaneous copied pages; All My Mountains by A. Donald Miller (1961); How They Found Christ by Rebecca J. Parker (1940); Whosoever chapters by Mary Warburten Booth (n.d.); First Fruits of the Forest by Betty Pritchard (n.d.); Willing Outcast by Pat Richards (n.d.); Together They Served: Mr. and Mrs. Fred Merian by Inez Spence (1960); Agnes and Christian Beckdahl On the Borders of Nepal by Inez Spence (n.d.)
    - H 01 02 01 and H 03 02 01 (11 titles), ca.1950-1979 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      These materials also have numbers in the Himalayan Collection Series A and F.
      Titles: The Duncan Hospital Raxaul by Trevor Strong and his wife (1952); Building at Raxaul by Trevor N. Strong and his wife (n.d.); The Regions Beyond Missionary Union: Rewards at Raxaul by Trevor Strong and his wife (n.d.); From Darkness to Light by Katharine Young (n.d.); Dharmi and her Bhotiya Family by Katharine Young (n.d.); Beauty for Ashes by Katharine Young (1964); Lengthen Thy Cords by Katharine Young (n.d.); The Fulfilment of a Promise by Katharine Young (1952); "First the Blade" - History fo the Institute of the Blessed Virgin Mary in India 1841-1962 by Mother Mary Colmcille (1968); Directory Diocese of Darjeeling (1989); Church History Shillong (1979)
    - H 02 02 01 (11 titles), 1946-1992 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      These matierals also have numbers in the Himalayan Collection in Series E.
      Titles: Bhutan - an Open Door: The Leprosy Mission by A. D. Askew (1967); Book in the native language; Indian and Nepali Children's Home: Darjeeling, N. Bengal, A Testimony by E. M. Beecroft (1946); Diocese of Darjeeling book in the native language (1985); Book in the native language; Souvenir on the Occasion of the Dedication Ceremony of "Anand Bhavan" in Kalimpong (1992); Golden Jubilee Celebration 1942-1992 Kalimpong (1992); On the Borders of Three Closed Lands by the Church of Scotland (n.d.); 55 Years in the Himalayas by H. C. Duncan (1957); Eastern Himalayas by the Church of Scotland Foreign Mission Committee (1945); Church of North India Darjeeling Diocese Constitution for Pastorates & Diocese (n.d.)
    - H 02 02 01 (6 titles), 1905-1986 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      These materials also have numbers in the Himalayan Collection in series E.
      Titles: Jesus Calls Crusade (1983); Dr. Craig's Research on the History fo the Church in the Eastern Himalayas (n.d.); Book in the native language; 50 Years of Gangtok Church 1936-1986 (1986); Fifty Wonderful Years Missionary Service in Foreign Lands: The India Field by Otto Christopher Grauer (1940); On the Threshold of Three Closed Lands: Chapter V by J. A. Graham (1905)
    - H 03 02 01 (13 titles), 1951-1996 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      These materials also have numbers in the Himalayan Collection in series F and K.
      Titles: History fo the Catholic Missions in North-East India 1890-1915 by C. Becker (1981); The Foundations of Catholic Mission Education in Manipur by Slaam Irene (n.d.); The Patna Mission Letter (1951); Roman Catholics and Shillong 1871-1890 by George Kottuppallil (1989); Roman Catholic Historiography in Northeast India by George Kottuppallil (n.d.); Roman Catholics in the Khasi Hills 1871-1890 by George Kottuppallil (n.d.); Roman Catholic Work Among the Garos 1911-1933 by George Kottuppallil (1990); Roman Catholic Work Among the Garos (1911-1933) by George Kottuppallil (n.d.); The First Phase of Roman Catholic Presence in the District of Darjeeling (1846-1900) by George Kottuppallil (1986); The Harvest Field of ASsam by P. C. Muanthanga (1996); A Souvenir of Centenary Pedong Parish 1882-1983 by M. Rey (1983); History of Catholic Church in Mizoram: 1925-1947 by Sangkima (1993); The Beginning of the Catholic Church among the Mizos by D. R. Syiemlieh (1993)
    - H 05 02 01 (13 titles), 1985-2002 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      These materials also have numbers in the Himalayan Collection, Series H.
      Titles: Amnesty International Information Catalogue (1991); Amnesty International: Bhutan Human Rights Violations (December, 1992); Amnesty International: Bhutan Forcible Exile (August, 1994); Amnesty International: People's Republi of China Human Rights Violations (May, 1992); Amnesty International: People's Republic of China The 1989 Pro-Democracy movement (May, 1992); Amnesty International: People's Republic of China Repression in Tibet (May, 1992); Amnesty International: People's Republic of China Concerns in Tibet (January, 1992); Amnesty International: China Repression in TIbet (May, 1992); Blessings International: Medicines for Missions in developing Nations (1993); Burma: Report on Human Rights Abuses (1993); Christianity in Chinland: by Khup Za Go (1985); Myanmar Indigenous Mission by Eddie Hang (1994); Findings Beyond the Border: Seasonal Migration Research in India by INF Mugu Programme (2002)
    - H 05 02 01 (16 titles), 1949-2001 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      Titles: Pahtau by J. W. Chyum Jawng Ma Hpung (1992); Christians in North India by James Massey (1987); The Burma Road from the Union of Burma to Myanmar by Mya Maung (1990); Directory of Churches & MIssions in India, Bakistan, Burma, and Ceylon: Section II (1949); Bhutan We Want Justice (n.d.); Bibliography of Christianity in Tibet by Cindy Perry (n.d.); A Brief History of Protestant Work in Dehra Dun by D. V. Singh (1967); The Tibetan Frontier Field by J. F. Swanson (1951); Papers of Myanmar Indigenous Mission by Pau Cin Thang (1993); Tibetan Buddhism (1998); The Tibetan Buddhist World (2001); History of Missions by Sam Moffett (n.d.); Pray for Myanmar (1996); Tribes and Nations Outreach (1994); A Tibetan Monk's Story (1995); 30 Days Hindu Prayer Focus (1998)
    - H 06 02 01 and H 07 02 01 (26 titles), 1990s (Box 64, Folder 3)
      These materials also have numbers in the Himalayan Collection, Series K and M.